Correspondence from the Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Foundation Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1894-1953 (Box 1-109)
  - Soria, Dario (Box-folder 92/7)
  - Sorkin, Leonard (Box-folder 92/8)
  - Sosen, Otto Ebel v. (Box-folder 92/9)
  - Soucek, Alfred (Box-folder 92/10)
  - Sousa, Eileen Adams (Box-folder 92/11)
  - South Mountain Association (Box-folder 92/12)
  - South Mountain Association: carbons of 1936 Aug. 27 letter; 1936 Sept. 2 letter; 1936 speech (Box-folder 92/13)
  - South Mountain Quartet (Box-folder 92/14)
  - Southern California Music Company (Box-folder 92/15)
  - Southern California Symphony Association see also Ussher, Bruno David (Box-folder 92/16)
  - Southern California. University (Box-folder 92/17)
  - Sowerby, Leo, 1916-1919 (Box-folder 92/18)
  - Sowerby, Leo, 1920-1928 (Box-folder 92/19)
  - Sowerby, Leo, undated (Box-folder 92/20)
  - "Sp" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 92/21)
  - Spalding, Albert (Box-folder 92/22)
  - Spalding, Henry and Nellie, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 92/23)
  - Spalding, Henry and Nellie, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 92/24)
  - Spalding, Henry and Nellie, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 92/25)
  - Spalding, Henry and Nellie, undated (Box-folder 92/26)
  - Spalding, Walter Raymond and Alexandrine, 1917-1929 (Box-folder 92/27)
  - Spalding, Walter Raymond and Alexandrine, 1930-1939 (Box-folder 92/28)
  - Spalding, Walter Raymond and Alexandrine, undated (Box-folder 92/29)
  - "Spe-Spr" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 93/1)
  - Speare, Mary, Dorothy and E. Ray (Box-folder 93/2)
  - Spelman, Timothy and Leolyn (Box-folder 93/3)
  - Spencer, Delta W. (Mrs. M. Donald Spencer) see Portland Symphony Society (Portland, Or.)
  - Spencer, Eleanor (Box-folder 93/4)
  - Speyer, Edward and Antonia (Box-folder 93/5)
  - Speyer, Louis and Camille, 1945 (Box-folder 93/6)
  - Speyer, Louis and Camille, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 93/7)
  - Speyer, Louis and Camille, 1948-1950 (Box-folder 93/8)
  - Speyer, Louis and Camille, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 93/9)
  - Speyer, Louis and Camille, undated (Box-folder 93/10)
  - Spicer, Earle (Box-folder 93/11)
  - Spiering, Theodore (Box-folder 93/12)
  - Spivacke, Harold see Library of Congress. Spivacke, Harold
  - Sprague, Albert A. and Mrs., 1923-1933 (Box-folder 93/13)
  - Sprague, Albert A. and Mrs., 1934-1939 (Box-folder 93/14)
  - Sprague, Albert A. and Mrs., 1940-1941 (Box-folder 93/15)
  - Sprague, Albert A. and Mrs., 1942-1944 (Box-folder 93/16)
  - Sprague, Albert A. and Mrs., 1945-1952 (Box-folder 93/17)
  - Sprague, Albert A. and Mrs., undated (Box-folder 93/18)
  - Sprague, Alice (Box-folder 93/19)
  - Sprague, Harriet (Mrs. Frank Sprague) (Box-folder 93/20)
  - Sprague, Laura (Box-folder 93/21)
  - Sprague, William H. (Box-folder 93/22)
  - Springer, J. Arthur (Box-folder 93/23)
  - Springfield, Massachusetts (Box-folder 93/24)
  - Sproul, Robert G. see California. University. Berkeley. Sproul, Robert Gordon and Ida
  - Spry, Walter (Box-folder 93/25)
  - "St" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 93/26)
  - Stad, Ben see also American Society of Ancient Instruments (Box-folder 93/27)
  - Stahl, Ruby Smith (Box-folder 93/28)
  - Stanford University. Allen, Warren D., 1928-1936 (Box-folder 94/1)
  - Stanford University. Allen, Warren D., 1937-1938 (Box-folder 94/2)
  - Stanford University. Allen, Warren D., 1939 (Box-folder 94/3)
  - Stanford University. Allen, Warren D., 1940-1946 (Box-folder 94/4)
  - Stanford University. Allen, Warren D., undated (Box-folder 94/5)
  - Stanford University. Barkan, Hans (Box-folder 94/6)
  - Stanford University. Crosten, William L. (Box-folder 94/7)
  - Stanford University. Friends of Music at Stanford, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 94/20)
  - Stanford University. Friends of Music at Stanford, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 94/21)
  - Stanford University. Friends of Music at Stanford, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 94/22)
  - Stanford University. Friends of Music at Stanford, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 94/23)
  - Stanford University. Friends of Music at Stanford, undated (Box-folder 94/24)
  - Stanford University. Hoover, Lou Henry (Box-folder 94/8)
  - Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys, 1917, 1933 (Box-folder 94/9)
  - Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys, 1934 (Box-folder 94/10)
  - Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys, 1935 (Box-folder 94/11)
  - Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys, 1936 (Box-folder 94/12)
  - Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 94/13)
  - Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys, 1939 (Box-folder 94/14)
  - Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys, 1940 (Box-folder 94/15)
  - Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys, 1941 (Box-folder 94/16)
  - Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys, 1942-1946 (Box-folder 94/17)
  - Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G. and Gladys, undated (Box-folder 94/18)
  - Stanford University. Wilbur, Ray Lyman (Box-folder 94/19)
  - Stanford University. Miscellany, 1933-1939 (Box-folder 94/25)
  - Stanford University. Miscellany, 1940-1950, undated (Box-folder 94/26)
  - Stanton, Roger see California Institute of Technology
  - "Ste" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 93/29)
  - Steeb, Olga (Box-folder 93/30)
  - Steele, Chauncey Depew see Cambridge, Mass. Miscellany (hotels)
  - Stefan, Paul see also International Society for Contemporary Music (Box-folder 93/31)
  - Stehlíkova, Dáda (Box-folder 93/32)
  - Stein, Joseph (Box-folder 93/33)
  - Steinert, Alexander Lang (Box-folder 93/34)
  - Steinert, M. and sons (Box-folder 93/35)
  - Steinhard, Erich (Box-folder 93/36)
  - Steinway & Sons (Box-folder 93/37)
  - "Sten-Stew" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 95/1)
  - Stengel-Sembrich, Marcella see Sembrich, Marcella
  - Štĕpán, Václav (Box-folder 95/2)
  - Stern, Isaac (letter to only) (Box-folder 95/3)
  - Stern, Rosalie (Mrs. Sigmund Stern), 1934-1939 (Box-folder 95/4)
  - Stern, Rosalie (Mrs. Sigmund Stern), 1940-1942 (Box-folder 95/5)
  - Stern, Rosalie (Mrs. Sigmund Stern), undated (Box-folder 95/6)
  - Stevens, Ethel Williams (Box-folder 95/7)
  - Stevens, Gorham P. and Mrs. (Box-folder 95/8)
  - Stevens, Halsey (Box-folder 95/9)
  - Stevenson, William C. (Box-folder 95/10)
  - "Sti" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 95/11)
  - Stier, Jean C. (Box-folder 95/12)
  - Still, William Grant (material on only) (Box-folder 95/13)
  - Stilwell, E.W. (Box-folder 95/14)
  - Stimson, Henry L. and Alice Bartlett (Box-folder 95/15)
  - "Sto" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 95/16)
  - Stock, Frederick A., 1915-1916 (Box-folder 95/17)
  - Stock, Frederick A., 1917-1918 (Box-folder 95/18)
  - Stock, Frederick A., 1919-1920 (Box-folder 95/19)
  - Stock, Frederick A., 1921-1924 (Box-folder 95/20)
  - Stock, Frederick A., 1925-1929 (Box-folder 95/21)
  - Stock, Frederick A., 1930-1933 (Box-folder 95/22)
  - Stock, Frederick A., 1934-1939 (Box-folder 95/23)
  - Stock, Frederick A., 1940-1943 (Box-folder 95/24)
  - Stock, Frederick A., undated (Box-folder 95/25)
  - Stock, Frederick Memorial Fund material see Frederick Stock Memorial Fund material
  - Stockbridge Bowl Association (Box-folder 95/27)
  - Stoddard, Nellie (Box-folder 95/28)
  - Stoeber, Emmeran and Sini, 1916-1919 (Box-folder 95/29)
  - Stoeber, Emmeran and Sini, 1922-1924 (Box-folder 95/30)
  - Stoeber, Emmeran and Sini, 1925 (Box-folder 95/31)
  - Stoeber, Emmeran and Sini, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 95/32)
  - Stoeber, Emmeran and Sini, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 95/33)
  - Stoeber, Emmeran and Sini, 1930-1939 (Box-folder 95/34)
  - Stoeber, Emmeran and Sini, 1940-1945 (Box-folder 95/35)
  - Stoeber, Emmeran and Sini, 1946-1953 (Box-folder 95/36)
  - Stoeber, Emmeran and Sini, undated (Box-folder 95/37)
  - Stoeckel, Carl (Box-folder 95/38)
  - Stoessel, Albert (Box-folder 95/39)
  - "Stoj-Stou" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 96/1)
  - Stojowski, Sigismond (Box-folder 96/2)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps (Box-folder 96/3)
  - Stokowski, Leopold (Box-folder 96/4)
  - Stokowski, Olga Samaroff, 1918-1929 (Box-folder 96/5)
  - Stokowski, Olga Samaroff, 1930-1950 (Box-folder 96/6)
  - Stokowski, Olga Samaroff, undated (Box-folder 96/7)
  - Stoll, Jessie Burns (Box-folder 96/8)
  - Stone, Harlan Fiske (Box-folder 96/9)
  - Stone, Herbert S. & co. (Box-folder 96/10)
  - Stone, Norman (Box-folder 96/11)
  - Stopak, Josef (Box-folder 96/12)
  - Story, Russell M. see Claremont College
  - "Str" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 96/13)
  - Strang, Gerald (Box-folder 96/14)
  - Stransky, Josef (Box-folder 96/15)
  - Stratton, Charles (Box-folder 96/16)
  - Strauss, Lawrence (Box-folder 96/17)
  - Stravinsky, Igor Fedorovich (Box-folder 96/18)
  - Strube, Gustav (Box-folder 96/19)
  - Strunk, Oliver see Library of Congress. Strunk, Oliver
  - "Stu-Sty" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 96/20)
  - "Su" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 96/21)
  - Suggia-Mena, Guilhermina (Box-folder 96/22)
  - Surette, Thomas Whitney (Box-folder 96/23)
  - Sutro, Rose and Ottilie (Box-folder 96/24)
  - Sutter, Otto Ernst (Box-folder 96/25)
  - Svečenski, Louis and Bertha, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 96/26)
  - Svečenski, Louis and Bertha, 1920-1924 (Box-folder 96/27)
  - Svečenski, Louis and Bertha, 1936-1953 (Box-folder 96/28)
  - Svečenski, Louis and Bertha, undated (Box-folder 96/29)
  - "Sw" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 96/30)
  - Swan, Alfred J. see Swarthmore College. Swan, Alfred J.
  - Swan, Howard see Occidental College. Swan, Howard
  - Swarthmore College. Swan, Alfred J. (Box-folder 96/31)
  - Swarthmore College. Miscellany (Box-folder 96/32)
  - Swarthout, Donald M. see Kansas, University of
  - Swing, Raymond (Box-folder 96/33)
  - Swoboda, Heinrich (Box-folder 96/34)
  - "Sy" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 96/35)
  - Sylva, Marguerita (Box-folder 96/36)
  - Symington, Maude Fay (Box-folder 96/37)
  - Synan, Mary (Box-folder 96/38)
  - "Sz" miscellaneous see also "S" miscellaneous (Box-folder 96/39)
  - Szántó, Théodore (Box-folder 96/40)
  - Szigeti, Joseph, 1928-1936 (Box-folder 96/41)
  - Szigeti, Joseph, 1937-1953 (Box-folder 96/42)
  - Szigeti, Joseph, undated (Box-folder 96/43)
  - Mrs. Coolidge's "S" see references (Box-folder 96/44)
  - "S" not further identified (Box-folder 96/45)
  - "T" miscellaneous (Box-folder 97/1)
  - Taft, Henry W. (Box-folder 97/2)
  - Taft, Ida see New York. Colony Club
  - Tailleferre, M. (Box-folder 97/3)
  - Talbott, Katharine H. (Box-folder 97/4)
  - Tallarico, Pasquale (Box-folder 97/5)
  - Tanglewood Music Center see Berkshire Music Center
  - Tansman, Alexandre, 1925-1939 (Box-folder 97/6)
  - Tansman, Alexandre, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 97/7)
  - Tansman, Alexandre, undated (Box-folder 97/8)
  - Taraba, B. (Box-folder 97/9)
  - Tas, Helen Teschner (Box-folder 97/10)
  - Taylor, Davidson see Columbia Broadcasting System. Taylor, Davidson
  - Taylor, Deems (Box-folder 97/11)
  - Taylor, Julia (Box-folder 97/12)
  - Taylor, Prentiss (Box-folder 97/13)
  - Tcherepnin, Alexander (Box-folder 97/14)
  - Tcherniawsky, Dora (Box-folder 97/15)
  - "Te" miscellaneous see also "T" miscellaneous (Box-folder 97/16)
  - Temianka, Henri, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 97/17)
  - Temianka, Henri, 1941 (Box-folder 97/18)
  - Temianka, Henri, 1942-1948 (Box-folder 97/19)
  - Temianka, Henri, 1950 (Box-folder 97/20)
  - Temianka, Henri, undated (Box-folder 97/21)
  - Tenney, Nathaniel and Ellie (Box-folder 97/22)
  - Tertis, Lionel and Ada, 1922 (Box-folder 97/23)
  - Tertis, Lionel and Ada, 1923 (Box-folder 97/24)
  - Tertis, Lionel and Ada, 1924 (Box-folder 97/25)
  - Tertis, Lionel and Ada, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 97/26)
  - Tertis, Lionel and Ada, 1927-1928 (Box-folder 97/27)
  - Tertis, Lionel and Ada, 1929 (Box-folder 97/28)
  - Tertis, Lionel and Ada, 1930 (Box-folder 97/29)
  - Tertis, Lionel and Ada, 1931-1933 (Box-folder 97/30)
  - Tertis, Lionel and Ada, 1934-1946 (Box-folder 97/31)
  - Tertis, Lionel and Ada, undated (Box-folder 97/32)
  - "Th" miscellaneous see also "T" miscellaneous (Box-folder 97/33)
  - Thacher, John see Dumbarton Oaks
  - The Thacher School (Box-folder 97/34)
  - Thackeray, Anne L. (Box-folder 97/35)
  - Thalheimer, R. E. (Box-folder 97/36)
  - Thaon di Revel, Irene see Revel, Irene Thaon di
  - "Thi-Thu" miscellaneous see also "T" miscellaneous (Box-folder 98/1)
  - Thibaud, Jacques (Box-folder 98/2)
  - Thomas, Edith M. (Box-folder 98/3)
  - Thomas, Norman (Box-folder 98/4)
  - Thomas, Theodore, Mrs. (Box-folder 98/5)
  - Thompson, Eliza (Mrs. W. David Thompson) (Box-folder 98/6)
  - Thompson, Julia W. (Box-folder 98/7)
  - Thompson, Oscar (Box-folder 98/8)
  - Thompson, Randall, 1927-1939 (Box-folder 98/9)
  - Thompson, Randall, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 98/10)
  - Thompson, Randall, 1943-1953 (Box-folder 98/11)
  - Thompson, Randall, undated (Box-folder 98/12)
  - Thomson, Virgil (material on) (Box-folder 98/13)
  - Thuotte, Gabriel (Box-folder 98/14)
  - Thurber, Clarence Howe see Redlands University
  - Thursfield, Anne, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 98/15)
  - Thursfield, Anne, 1927-1943 (Box-folder 98/16)
  - Thursfield, Anne, undated (Box-folder 98/17)
  - Thurston, Clara Louise (Box-folder 98/18)
  - "Ti" miscellaneous see also "T" miscellaneous (Box-folder 98/19)
  - Tibaldi Chiesa, Mary (Box-folder 98/20)
  - Tietz, Frederic, Jr. (Box-folder 98/21)
  - Tilton, Edith Rhetts see Detroit Symphony Orchestra
  - Timmner, Anna Maria (Box-folder 98/22)
  - Tinayre, Yves, 1931-1946 (Box-folder 98/23)
  - Tinayre, Yves, 1947-1950 (Box-folder 98/24)
  - Tinlot, Gustave (Box-folder 98/25)
  - Tobin, Richard Montgomery, 1932-1935 (Box-folder 98/26)
  - Tobin, Richard Montgomery, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 98/27)
  - Tobin, Richard Montgomery, undated (Box-folder 98/28)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly: material concerning 1934 New School project see also New School for Social Research (Box-folder 99/1)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1937 (Box-folder 99/2)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1938 (Box-folder 99/3)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1939 (Box-folder 99/4)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1940 (Box-folder 99/5)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1941 (Box-folder 99/6)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1942 (Box-folder 99/7)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1943 (Box-folder 99/8)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1944 (Box-folder 99/9)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1945 (Box-folder 99/10)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1946 (Box-folder 99/11)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1947 (Box-folder 99/12)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1948 (Box-folder 99/13)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1949 (Box-folder 99/14)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1950 (Box-folder 99/15)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1951 (Box-folder 99/16)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 99/17)
  - Toch, Ernst and Lilly, undated (Box-folder 99/18)
  - "Tod-Toz" miscellaneous see also "T" miscellaneous (Box-folder 100/1)
  - Tollefsen, Carl H. (Box-folder 100/2)
  - Tomasow, Jan (Box-folder 100/3)
  - Tomes, Margaret Frances (Box-folder 100/4)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, Carla and Wanda, Includes telegrams. (Box-folder 100/5)
  - Tourret, André (Box-folder 100/6)
  - Tovey, Donald Francis (Box-folder 100/7)
  - Town Hall see New York. Town Hall
  - Townsend, Natalie (Box-folder 100/8)
  - "Tr" miscellaneous see also "T" miscellaneous (Box-folder 100/9)
  - Traller, Iren (Box-folder 100/10)
  - Trampler, Walter see New Music String Quartet
  - Traver, Hope (Box-folder 100/11)
  - Treacy, Alma K. (Box-folder 100/12)
  - Trend, J.B. (Box-folder 100/13)
  - Troccoli, Federico (Box-folder 100/14)
  - Troubetskoi, Princess Alexander (Box-folder 100/15)
  - Trowbridge, Alfred Lockwood and Mrs. (Box-folder 100/16)
  - Tryon, Winthrop P. (Box-folder 100/17)
  - "Tu" miscellaneous see also "T" miscellaneous (Box-folder 100/18)
  - Tucker, George H. (Box-folder 100/19)
  - Tucker, Gregory and Elizabeth (Box-folder 100/20)
  - Tufts College (Box-folder 100/21)
  - Turner, Godfrey (Box-folder 100/22)
  - Turner, Helen (Mrs. William Jay Turner) (Box-folder 100/23)
  - Tuskegee Institute (Box-folder 100/24)
  - Tuthill, Burnet Corwin, 1915-1934 (Box-folder 100/25)
  - Tuthill, Burnet Corwin, 1935-1953, undated (Box-folder 100/26)
  - Tuthill, William Burnet (Box-folder 100/27)
  - Tuttle, Mabel C. (Box-folder 100/28)
  - Tuyll, Corrie de (Box-folder 100/29)
  - "Tw-Ty" miscellaneous see also "T" miscellaneous (Box-folder 100/30)
  - Tweedy, Donald N. (Box-folder 100/31)
  - Twentieth Century Fox (Box-folder 100/32)
  - Twichell, Roger Thayer see Browne & Nichols School, Cambridge, Massachusetts
  - Tyler, Cornelius Boardman and Susan W. (Box-folder 100/33)
  - "T" not further identified; and Mrs. Coolidge's "T" "see" references (Box-folder 100/34)
  - "U" miscellaneous (Box-folder 100/35)
  - Ulher, Mrs. Otto (this is a "ghost" for Neher, Edna) (Box-folder 100/36)
  - Ulke, Titus (Box-folder 100/37)
  - Union for Democratic Action (Box-folder 100/38)
  - United Nations Fund of the American Association for the United Nations, Inc., Contains additional items relating to the United Nations. (Box-folder 100/39)
  - United Negro College Fund (Box-folder 100/40)
  - United States. Customs Service (Box-folder 100/41)
  - United States. Dept. of State (Box-folder 100/45)
  - United States. Immigration and Naturalization Service, Contains additional items relating to immigration. (Box-folder 100/42)
  - U.S. Inaugural Ball Committee, 1933 (Box-folder 100/43)
  - United States Naval Academy, Contains additional items relating to the U.S. Navy. (Box-folder 100/44)
  - United States. Works Progress Administration (Box-folder 100/46)
  - United States of America. Miscellany (Box-folder 100/47)
  - Universal Edition (Vienna, Austria) see also Hertzka, Emil (Box-folder 100/48)
  - Université de Lausanne see Lausanne. Université
  - University of California, Berkeley see California. University. Berkeley
  - University of Chicago see Chicago University
  - University of Colorado, Boulder see Colorado. University
  - University of Georgia see Georgia. University
  - University of Kansas see Kansas, University of
  - University of North Carolina see North Carolina. University
  - University of Redlands see Redlands University
  - University of Southern California see Southern California. University
  - University of Vermont see Vermont University
  - University of Virginia see Virginia. University
  - University of Washington see Washington (State) University
  - University of Wisconsin see Wisconsin. University
  - Untermeyer, Eugene, Mrs. (Box-folder 100/49)
  - Upton, William Treat (Box-folder 100/50)
  - Urania (Volkshochschule: Graz, Austria) see Grazer Urania
  - Urchs, Ernest (Box-folder 100/51)
  - Urey, Harold C. (Box-folder 100/52)
  - Urner, Catherine (Box-folder 100/53)
  - "Us" (empty) (Box-folder 101/1)
  - Usigli, Gastone (Box-folder 101/2)
  - Ussher, Bruno David, 1927-1929 (Box-folder 101/3)
  - Ussher, Bruno David, 1930-1934 (Box-folder 101/4)
  - Ussher, Bruno David, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 101/5)
  - Ussher, Bruno David, 1938-1946 (Box-folder 101/6)
  - Ussher, Bruno David, undated (Box-folder 101/7)
  - Utah State Institute of Fine Arts, Includes other items relating to Utah. (Box-folder 101/8)
  - Utgoff, Tamara (Box-folder 101/9)
  - "V" miscellaneous (Box-folder 101/10)
  - Vaes, Tony (Box-folder 101/11)
  - Valéry, Paul (Box-folder 101/12)
  - Valis, Mary (Box-folder 101/13)
  - Vallas, Léon (Box-folder 101/14)
  - "Van-Vau" miscellaneous see also "V" miscellaneous (Box-folder 101/15)
  - Van den Burg, William (Box-folder 101/16)
  - van der Hoeven, C. (Box-folder 101/17)
  - Vanderlip, Narcissa Cox (Box-folder 101/18)
  - Van der Voort, R. (Box-folder 101/19)
  - Van Doorn, Albert (Box-folder 101/20)
  - Van Vliet, Cornelius (Box-folder 101/21)
  - Varèse, Edgard (Box-folder 101/22)
  - Vaska, Bedrich (Box-folder 101/23)
  - Vassar College (Box-folder 101/24)
  - Vaughan Williams, Ralph (Box-folder 101/25)
  - "Ve" miscellaneous see also "V" miscellaneous (Box-folder 101/26)
  - Veissi, Jasche (Box-folder 101/27)
  - Venables, Mary (Box-folder 101/28)
  - Venice (Box-folder 101/29)
  - Verhuyck-Coulon, Gaston, 1926-1929 (Box-folder 101/30)
  - Verhuyck-Coulon, Gaston, 1931-1935 (Box-folder 101/31)
  - Verhuyck-Coulon, Gaston, 1936-1939 (Box-folder 101/32)
  - Verhuyck-Coulon, Gaston, 1940-1946 (Box-folder 101/33)
  - Verhuyck-Coulon, Gaston, undated (Box-folder 101/34)
  - Vermuelen, Matthys (Box-folder 101/35)
  - Vermont University (Box-folder 101/36)
  - Verrall, John (Box-folder 101/37)
  - "Vi" miscellaneous see also "V" miscellaneous (Box-folder 101/38)
  - Vidal, Paul (Box-folder 101/39)
  - Vieland, Josef (Box-folder 101/40)
  - Vielle Trio (Box-folder 101/41)
  - Vienna (Box-folder 101/42)
  - Vienna. Gesellschaft der Musikfreunde (Box-folder 101/43)
  - Virginia. University, Includes additional material related to Virginia. (Box-folder 101/44)
  - "Vo" miscellaneous see also "V" miscellaneous (Box-folder 101/45)
  - Voegeli, Henry Edward see Chicago Symphony Orchestra
  - Voegtlin, Lilian (Box-folder 101/46)
  - Vogt, A.S. (Box-folder 101/47)
  - Vredenburg, Max (Box-folder 101/49)
  - Vronsky, Vitya (Box-folder 101/48)
  - Mrs. Coolidge's "V" "see" references (Box-folder 101/50)
  - "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 102/1)
  - WCRB (Radio station: Waltham, Mass.) (Box-folder 102/2)
  - WNYC see New York. Municipal Broadcasting System
  - Wagenaar, Bernard (Box-folder 102/3)
  - Wagner, Charles L. (Box-folder 102/4)
  - Wagner, Joseph (Box-folder 102/5)
  - Waite, Marjorie (Box-folder 102/6)
  - Waith, William S. (Box-folder 102/7)
  - "Wal" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 102/8)
  - Walcott, Frederic C. (Box-folder 102/9)
  - Walcott, Mary Vaux (Box-folder 102/10)
  - Walevitch, Anne Whelpley (Box-folder 102/11)
  - Walker, Dorothea E. (Box-folder 102/12)
  - Walker, Dorothy L. (Box-folder 102/13)
  - Walker, Ernest (Box-folder 102/14)
  - Walker, Herschel C. and Mrs. (Box-folder 102/15)
  - Wall, Vivian (Box-folder 102/16)
  - Walle, [Emily?] F. (Box-folder 102/17)
  - Walter, Bruno (Box-folder 102/18)
  - Walter, Margaret (Box-folder 102/19)
  - Walter, William E. (Box-folder 102/20)
  - Wambaugh, Mary and Sarah (Box-folder 102/21)
  - Wands, Lulu A. (Box-folder 102/22)
  - "War" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 102/23)
  - Warburg, Felix M. (and other family members) (Box-folder 102/24)
  - Ward, Lydia (Box-folder 102/25)
  - Warden, Sherman, 1933-1939 (Box-folder 102/26)
  - Warden, Sherman, 1940-1947 (Box-folder 102/27)
  - Warden, Sherman, undated (Box-folder 102/28)
  - Warlich, Reinhold von (Box-folder 102/29)
  - Warner, H. Waldo (Box-folder 102/30)
  - Warner, Langdon, Mrs. (Box-folder 102/31)
  - Warnery, Edmond (Box-folder 102/34)
  - Warren, Cinina Brescia (Box-folder 102/32)
  - Warren, Robert Penn (Box-folder 102/33)
  - Washington Cathedral see National Cathedral
  - Washington, D.C. see also District of Columbia
  - Washington, D.C. Arts Club (Box-folder 102/35)
  - Washington, D.C. Composers Club (Box-folder 102/36)
  - Washington, D.C. Conservatory of Music and School of Expression see Marshall, Harriet Gibbs
  - Washington, D.C. Freer Gallery of Art see Guest, Grace Dunham
  - Washington, D.C. Friday Morning Music Club (Box-folder 102/37)
  - Washington, D.C. hotels: Mayflower (Box-folder 102/38)
  - Washington, D.C. hotels: 2400 16th Street, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 102/39)
  - Washington, D.C. hotels: 2400 16th Street, 1937-1942 (Box-folder 102/40)
  - Washington, D.C. hotels: 2400 16th Street, 1943-1949 (Box-folder 102/41)
  - Washington, D.C. hotels: 2400 16th Street, undated and fragmentary (Box-folder 102/42)
  - Washington, D.C. hotels: miscellany (Box-folder 102/43)